Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files C
    - Cooper, Andrew W. (Box A-27, Folder 127)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Pictorial Enterprise, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Rufus Merritt,
    - Cooper, Andrew W. (Box A-27, Folder 128)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Dave Greene
    - Contemporary Women (Box A-27, Folder 129)
      2 typescript leaves with ms. notes stapled to recto of print.
      Photographer if identified: Ray A. Moss
    - The Contessas (Box A-27, Folder 130)
    - Pretty Contestants (Box A-27, Folder 131)
    - Continental Baking Co. (Box A-27, Folder 132)
    - Continental Society of N.Y. (Box A-27, Folder 133)
      Typescript caption attached to recto of print with staple. 1 print has press release stapled to verso. 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Jaime, Al Burley, James Gilbert, Layne's Studio, James C. Campbell
    - Continental (4) (Box A-27, Folder 134)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Denning
    - The Continentals (Box A-27, Folder 135)
      1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 3 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, A. Hansen, Layne's Studio, James C. Campbell, L. St. Clair Dummett, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Conrad, Barbara Smith (Box A-27, Folder 136)
    - Astronaut Conrad, Charles (Box A-27, Folder 137)
      2 NASA prints have biographical info printed on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Thomas Aaron, NASA
    - Contours (Box A-27, Folder 138)
    - The Contract (Box A-27, Folder 139)
    - Contractors (Box A-27, Folder 140)
      2 ms. leaves attached to group of prints with paper clips.
    - Convention, Democratic '84 (Box A-27, Folder 141)
    - Convention, Republican '84 (Box A-27, Folder 142)
    - Convissor, Samuel M. (Box A-27, Folder 143)
    - Conway, Agnes Mrs. (Box A-27, Folder 144)
    - Conway, Aviva (Box A-27, Folder 145)
    - Conway, Blanche (Box A-27, Folder 146)
    - Conway, Charlie (Box A-27, Folder 147)
    - Conway, Gloria (Box A-27, Folder 148)
    - Conway, Fr. Robert F. (Box A-27, Folder 149)
    - Conwill, Houston (Box A-27, Folder 150)
    - Conyers, John (Box A-27, Folder 151)
    - Conyers, Sammy (Box A-27, Folder 152)
    - Cooey, Billie L. (Box A-27, Folder 153)
      Photographer if identified: Harold Stovall
    - Cook, Bill (Box A-27, Folder 154)
      Photographer if identified: Turner's Photo Studio
    - Cook, Calvin C. Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-27, Folder 155)
    - Cook, C. W. (Box A-27, Folder 156)
    - Cook, Charles (Box A-27, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Paule-Epstein
    - Cook, Christine (Box A-27, Folder 158)
    - Cook, Cookie (Box A-27, Folder 159)
    - Cook, "Cookie" (Box A-27, Folder 160)
    - Cook, Daniel R. (Box A-27, Folder 161)
    - Cook, David A. (Box A-27, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: Western Electric Photographic Service
    - Cook, Donald C. (Box A-27, Folder 163)
    - Cook, Dwight (Box A-27, Folder 164)
    - Cook, Rev. Ernest (Box A-27, Folder 165)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James Gilbert, A. Hansen
    - Cook, Ernest T. (Box A-27, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: Rapid News Photo Service/W. Smith
    - Cook, Flossie (Box A-27, Folder 167)
    - Cook, Francis F. (Box A-27, Folder 168)
    - Cook, Frank (Rev.) (Box A-27, Folder 169)
    - Cook, Fred (Box A-27, Folder 170)
    - Cook, Gerald (Box A-27, Folder 171)
      Photographer if identified: Marcus Blechman
    - Cook, Howard W. (Box A-27, Folder 172)
      Press release about 50-year retiree attached to print with paper clip.
    - Cook, Inez (Box A-27, Folder 173)
    - Cook, J. D. (Box A-27, Folder 174)
      Typescript caption stapled to recto of print.
    - Cook, J. E. (Box A-27, Folder 175)
      Photographer if identified: P. Ballentine and Sons
    - Cook, J. Lawrence (Box A-27, Folder 176)
      2 prints are mounted on matte, which has a newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    - Cook, James (Box A-27, Folder 177)
      Photographer if identified: Randy Abbott
    - Cook, James D. (Box A-27, Folder 178)
    - Cook, Samuel DuBois Dr. (Box A-27, Folder 179)
      Photographer if identified: News Office, Dillard U.
    - Cook, Jean L. Dr. (Box A-27, Folder 180)
    - Cook, Jim (Box A-27, Folder 181)
    - Cook, John (Box A-27, Folder 182)
    - Cook, Joy (Mrs.) (Box A-27, Folder 183)
    - Cook, Ladda B. (Box A-27, Folder 184)
      Photographer if identified: George Jervas Photo Studio, Bunny Photo Studio
    - Cook, Lawrence (Box A-27, Folder 185)
    - Cook, Mattie Dr. (Box A-27, Folder 186)
      Photographer if identified: John Maguire/Matar Studio
    - Cook, Mercer (Box A-27, Folder 187)
    - Cook, Robert L. (Box A-27, Folder 189)
    - Cook, Samuel DuBois Dr. (Box A-27, Folder 190)
      Photographer if identified: Norman Berteaux, News Office, Dillard U.
    - Cook, Shirley (Box A-27, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Foto-Ottica Saglimbene
    - Cook, Sylvester (Box A-27, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.R.A. Photo/Bob Coglianese
    - Cook, Terry (Box A-27, Folder 193)
    - Cook, Vivian (Box A-27, Folder 194)
    - Cook, William S. (Box A-27, Folder 195)
    - Cooke, Alistair (Box A-27, Folder 196)
    - Cooke, Anne M. (Box A-27, Folder 197)
    - Cooke, Ardena (Box A-27, Folder 198)
    - Cooke, Ardrena (Box A-27, Folder 199)
    - Cooke, Aubrey Smith Jr. (Box A-27, Folder 200)
    - Cooke, Bill (Washboard) (Box A-27, Folder 201)
    - Cooke, Bonnie (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-27, Folder 202)
    - Cooke, C. W. (Box A-27, Folder 203)
    - Cecil Cooke (Box A-27, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Inge Hardison, Sepia Art Inc.
    - Cooke, Charles L. Dr. (Box A-27, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: Theodor Stolar
    - Cooke, Charles & L.C. (Box A-27, Folder 206)
    - Cooke, Clifford (Box A-27, Folder 207)
    - Cooke, Clifford M. (Box A-27, Folder 208)
    - Cooke, Francis Cardinal (Box A-27, Folder 209)
    - Cooke, Cardinal (Box A-27, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: Jim Curry
    - Cooke, Fred Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-27, Folder 211)
    - Herbert Cooke (Box A-27, Folder 212)
      Photographer if identified: Merritt & Baldwin Studio
    - Cooke, Jack Kent (Box A-27, Folder 213)
    - Cooke, James (Box A-27, Folder 214)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Layne Photo
    - Cooke, John D. (Box A-27, Folder 215)
    - Cooke, Leonard (Box A-27, Folder 216)
    - Cook, Ladda (Box A-27, Folder 217)
    - Cooke, Lloyd Dr. (Box A-27, Folder 218)
    - Cooke, Marie (Box A-27, Folder 219)
    - Dr. Cook, Mattie (Box A-27, Folder 220)
    - Cooke, Mary Virginia (Box A-27, Folder 221)
    - Cooke, Mercer (Box A-27, Folder 222)
    - Cooke, Norma (Box A-27, Folder 223)
    - Cooke, Raglan P. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-27, Folder 224)
      Photographer if identified: William W. Gilbert
    - Cooke, Sam (Box A-27, Folder 225)
    - Cooke, Sam (Franklin, Bertha killer) (Box A-27, Folder 226)
    - Cooke, Terence J. The Most Rev. (Box A-27, Folder 227)
    - Cooke, Thomas (Mayor) (Box A-27, Folder 228)
    - Cooke, Tom (Box A-27, Folder 229)
    - Cooking (Box A-27, Folder 230)
      3 halftone prints.
    - Carlos A. Cooks (Box A-27, Folder 231)
    - "The Cool World" (Box A-27, Folder 232)
      Photographer if identified: Leroy McLukas
    - Cooley, Archie (Box A-27, Folder 233)
    - Cooley, Isabelle (Box A-27, Folder 234)
    - Cooley, Jane and Clarice Graham (Box A-27, Folder 235)
      Photographer if identified: Rapid News Photo Service/Nichols
    - Cools, Mildred D. (Box A-27, Folder 236)
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell, Camera Paintings-Photographs
    - Coombe, Audrey (Box A-27, Folder 237)
    - Coombs, Anita (Box A-27, Folder 238)
    - Coombs, Blanche (Box A-27, Folder 239)
    - Coombs, Delores Mrs. (Box A-27, Folder 240)
    - Coombs, Dolores (Box A-27, Folder 241)
    - Coombs, Harold (Box A-27, Folder 242)
    - Coombs, Harry (Box A-27, Folder 243)
      Photographer if identified: Columbia Records
    - Coombs, Orde (Box A-27, Folder 244)
    - Coombs, Ralph (Box A-27, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, Rapid News Photo/Hawkins
    - Coombs, Shelton (Box A-27, Folder 246)
    - Coomer, Harold (Box A-27, Folder 247)
    - Coon, James (Box A-27, Folder 248)
    - Cooney, Gerry (Box A-27, Folder 249)
    - Cooney, Gerry (Box A-27, Folder 250)
    - Cooney, James (Box A-27, Folder 251)
    - "Coonskin" (Box A-27, Folder 252)
    - Cooper, Al (Box A-27, Folder 253)
    - Cooper, Bennett (Box A-28, Folder 1)
    - Cooper, Blondell (Box A-28, Folder 2)
    - Cooper, Cecilia (Box A-28, Folder 3)
      Also one halftone print copy.
      Photographer if identified: Aviation News Services
    - Cooper, Charles (Box A-28, Folder 4)
    - Cooper, Charles (Box A-28, Folder 5)
    - Cooper, Christina (Box A-28, Folder 6)
    - Cooper, Chuck (Box A-28, Folder 7)
    - Cooper, Clarence (Box A-28, Folder 8)
      Photographer if identified: Matt Grimaldi
    - Cooper, Clarence E. (Box A-28, Folder 9)
    - Cooper Clothing Store (Box A-28, Folder 10)
      1946
    - Cooper, Cornelius (Lt.) (Box A-28, Folder 11)
    - Cooper, Cottrell (Box A-28, Folder 12)
      Photographer if identified: Photokraft
    - Cooper, Damon (Box A-28, Folder 13)
      Also black and white negatives in a small envelope
    - Cooper, David (Box A-28, Folder 14)
    - Cooper, Doryce Brown (Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 15)
    - Cooper, Edith Lee (See Wm. Kendricks) (Box A-28, Folder 16)
    - Cooper, Edwin L. (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 17)
    - Cooper, Emmett, Jr. (Box A-28, Folder 18)
      Photographer if identified: Post Office Dept. Photo
    - Cooper, Emmett G. (Box A-28, Folder 19)
    - Cooper, Ethelyn (Box A-28, Folder 20)
    - Cooper, Edwin (Box A-28, Folder 21)
    - Cooper, Ellen D. (Box A-28, Folder 22)
    - Cooper, Eugene (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 23)
    - Cooper, Evelyn (Box A-28, Folder 24)
    - Cooper, Gary (Box A-28, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: Metropolitan Photo Service Inc.
    - Cooper, George Clinton (Box A-28, Folder 26)
    - Cooper, Gladys (Box A-28, Folder 27)
    - Cooper, Gary (Box A-28, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of both the actor and of a basketball player.
    - Cooper, L. Gordon (Box A-28, Folder 29)
    - Cooper, G. Gordon (Box A-28, Folder 30)
    - Cooper, Harold (Box A-28, Folder 31)
    - Cooper, Hather S. (Box A-28, Folder 32)
    - Cooper, Helen (Box A-28, Folder 33)
      Enlarged color kodachrome enlargement. Also one velox print.
    - Cooper, Helmar (Box A-28, Folder 34)
      Photographer if identified: Errol Bonadie
    - Cooper, Helyn L. (Box A-28, Folder 35)
    - Cooper, Herman (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 36)
    - Cooper, Jackie (Box A-28, Folder 37)
    - Cooper, Jackson H. (Sr.) (Box A-28, Folder 38)
      Photographer if identified: Pan American World Airways System
    - Cooper, Jerome (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: John Gardner
    - Cooper, Jocelyn (Box A-28, Folder 40)
      Photographer if identified: John L. Clark
    - Cooper, John (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 41)
    - Cooper, John L (Box A-28, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: Irene B. Bayer
    - Cooper, John W. (Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 43)
    - Cooper, Joseph N. (Box A-28, Folder 44)
      Photographer if identified: Image
    - Cooper, Lawrence (Box A-28, Folder 45)
    - Cooper, Lee (Box A-28, Folder 46)
    - Cooper, Lee (Box A-28, Folder 47)
    - Cooper, Lela Douglas (Box A-28, Folder 48)
    - Cooper, Lisa (Box A-28, Folder 49)
    - Cooper, Marc (Box A-28, Folder 50)
    - Cooper, Margo (Box A-28, Folder 51)
    - Cooper, Mary Ellen (Box A-28, Folder 52)
    - Cooper, Maudine R. (Box A-28, Folder 53)
    - Cooper, Mickey (Box A-28, Folder 54)
    - Cooper, Nat (Box A-28, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Alex Hamilton, King Photographers
    - Cooper, Paul (Box A-28, Folder 56)
      Photographer if identified: Lora
    - Cooper, Peggy (Box A-28, Folder 57)
    - Cooper, Peter (Box A-28, Folder 58)
    - Cooper, Phyllis (Box A-28, Folder 59)
    - Cooper, Ralph (Box A-28, Folder 60)
    - Cooper, Ralph (V) (Box A-28, Folder 61)
    - Cooper, Quincy B. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 62)
    - Cooper, Ralph (Box A-28, Folder 63)
      Ralph Cooper is identified as the photographer on some prints.
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Cooper, George West
    - Cooper, Raymond J. (Box A-28, Folder 64)
    - Cooper, Robert (Box A-28, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph B. Kessler, Studio Reneé, New York City Youth Board
    - Cooper, Roscoe (Box A-28, Folder 66)
    - Cooper, Ruth (Box A-28, Folder 67)
    - Cooper, Sidney (Box A-28, Folder 68)
    - Cooper, Stephen H. (Box A-28, Folder 69)
    - Cooper Quartet, Steve (Box A-28, Folder 70)
    - Cooper, Tarzan (Box A-28, Folder 71)
    - Cooper, Tony (Box A-28, Folder 72)
    - Cooper, Walter (Box A-28, Folder 73)
    - Cooper, Walter (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 74)
    - Cooper, Wayman (Mrs.) (See Mrs. Charles Stewart) (Box A-28, Folder 75)
    - Cooper, William (Box A-28, Folder 76)
    - Cooper, William (See Robert [Ross?]) (Box A-28, Folder 77)
    - Cooper, William (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 78)
    - Cooper Park Day (Box A-28, Folder 79)
      Photographer if identified: Alex Simmons
    - Cooper Union (Box A-28, Folder 80)
    - Cooper Warriors (Box A-28, Folder 81)
    - Cooper, William B. (Box A-28, Folder 82)
    - Cooper, Al (Box A-28, Folder 83)
    - Coordinating Committee of Women's Clubs (Box A-28, Folder 84)
    - Coordinators, The (Box A-28, Folder 85)
    - Coore, David (Hon.) (Box A-28, Folder 86)
    - Copage, Marc (Box A-28, Folder 87)
    - Copasetics Club (Box A-28, Folder 88)
    - Cope, Hobart (Box A-28, Folder 89)
    - Cope, William B. (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 90)
    - Copeland, Bobby (Box A-28, Folder 91)
    - Copeland, Calvin (Box A-28, Folder 92)
      Three prints are stuck together with scotch tape. One color photo with Richard Pryor.
    - Copeland, Cheryl (Box A-28, Folder 93)
    - Copedge, Margo (Box A-28, Folder 94)
    - Copeland, Ernest (Box A-28, Folder 95)
    - Copeland, Ernie (Box A-28, Folder 96)
    - Copeland, Gigi (Box A-28, Folder 97)
    - Copeland, Hunter B., Jr. (Box A-28, Folder 98)
      Photographer if identified: Peter A. Russo/Fort Wadsworth Photo Facility, Signal Photo Facility/Fort Hamilton NY
    - Copeland, Inez (Box A-28, Folder 99)
    - Copeland, Joe (Box A-28, Folder 100)
    - Copeland, Kyle (Box A-28, Folder 101)
    - Copeland, Larry (Box A-28, Folder 102)
    - Copeland, Lawrence (Box A-28, Folder 103)
    - Copeland, Narcissus (Box A-28, Folder 104)
    - Copeland, Raymond (Box A-28, Folder 105)
    - Copeland, Rose Harrison (Box A-28, Folder 106)
    - Copeland, Roy (Box A-28, Folder 107)
    - Copeland, Saundra (Box A-28, Folder 108)
    - Copeland, Sylvia (Box A-28, Folder 109)
      Photographer if identified: Boris Bakchy, Dorothy Ross
    - Copeland, Vanessa (Box A-28, Folder 110)
    - Copeland, William (Box A-28, Folder 111)
    - Copeland, William (Box A-28, Folder 112)
      Typescript description on verso - subject wanted for murder.
    - Copeman, Chester (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 113)
      One print, badly darkened and giving off a chemical odor.
    - Co-Petites Social Club (Box A-28, Folder 114)
    - Coppin, Joyce R. (Box A-28, Folder 115)
    - Coran, Joyce (Box A-28, Folder 116)
    - Coray, Lindsey (Box A-28, Folder 117)
    - Corbett, Clementine (Box A-28, Folder 118)
    - Corbett, Ellis (Box A-28, Folder 119)
    - Corbett, James (Box A-28, Folder 120)
    - Corbie, Leo A. (Box A-28, Folder 121)
    - Corbin, Anna (Box A-28, Folder 122)
    - Corbin, Clayton (Box A-28, Folder 123)
    - Corbin, Darnley (Box A-28, Folder 124)
    - Corbin, Davis (Box A-28, Folder 125)
    - Cordero, John (The Very Rev.) (Box A-28, Folder 126)
    - Cordice, Marguerite (Box A-28, Folder 127)
    - Cordy, Linda (See Mrs. Carl Williams) (Box A-28, Folder 128)
    - Core, Traci (Box A-28, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Joe DeAngello
    - C.O.R.E. (See: Congress of Racial Equality) (Box A-28, Folder 130)
    - Core, David (Box A-28, Folder 131)
    - Corea, Chick (Box A-28, Folder 132)
    - Coreton, Bill (Box A-28, Folder 133)
    - Corey, Edward L. (Box A-28, Folder 134)
    - Corinaldi, Austin (Box A-28, Folder 135)
    - Coriolan, Beatrice (Box A-28, Folder 136)
    - Cornick, Imogene (Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 137)
    - Cormier, Lawrence J. (Box A-28, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Gill Photographers
    - Cornelius, Charles H. (Box A-28, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: University of Hartford/News Bureau
    - Cornelius, Don (Box A-28, Folder 140)
    - Cornelius, El Anna (Box A-28, Folder 141)
    - Cornelius, Foster (Box A-28, Folder 142)
    - Cornelius, Samuel J. (Box A-28, Folder 143)
    - Cornely, Paul B. (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 144)
    - Corning, Erastus (Mayor) (Box A-28, Folder 145)
    - Cornish, Frank (See Willie Young) (Box A-28, Folder 146)
    - Cornute, Carmen (Box A-28, Folder 147)
    - Cornwall, Robert (Box A-28, Folder 148)
    - Coronet Women's Club of New York (Box A-28, Folder 149)
    - Coronation Ball (Box A-28, Folder 150)
    - Correa, Djalma (Box A-28, Folder 151)
      Photographer if identified: Marcos Sacchi
    - Correction Officers Benevolent Association (Box A-28, Folder 152)
      Newspaper clipping adhered to verso of one print.
    - Corrin, Lois Beatrice (Box A-28, Folder 153)
    - Corrin, Malcolm L. (Box A-28, Folder 154)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley, Jim Curry, Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, R.E. Condit Studio, Aristocrat Studio
    - Corrington, Gerry (Box A-28, Folder 155)
      Photographer if identified: Barney Weinberg
    - Corsey, Nolan L. (Box A-28, Folder 156)
    - Cosby, Bill (Box A-28, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Sharon Inc., United Press International, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Cosby, Bill (Box A-28, Folder 158)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, United Air Lines
    - Cosby, Bill (Box A-28, Folder 159)
    - Cosby, Bill (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 160)
    - "Cosby Show, The Bill" (Box A-28, Folder 161)
      Includes one glossy color clipping on light stock.
    - Corsey, Priscilla (Box A-28, Folder 162)
    - Cortez, Dave "Baby" (Box A-28, Folder 163)
    - Corum, Jack (Box A-28, Folder 164)
    - Cortez, Elizabeth (Box A-28, Folder 165)
    - Cosby, Lillian (Box A-28, Folder 166)
    - Cosell, Howard (Box A-28, Folder 167)
    - Cosburn, Henry S. (Box A-28, Folder 168)
    - Coslen, Russell (Box A-28, Folder 169)
    - "Cosmic Energy" (Box A-28, Folder 170)
    - Cosmic Echoes (Box A-28, Folder 171)
    - Costa, Birdella (Box A-28, Folder 172)
    - Costa, Marjorie (Box A-28, Folder 173)
    - Costas, Mildred (Box A-28, Folder 174)
    - Costello, Deloris (Box A-28, Folder 175)
    - Costello, Henrietta, (Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 176)
    - Costen, Bill (Box A-28, Folder 177)
    - Costen, Russell (Box A-28, Folder 178)
    - Costin, Marjorie A. (Box A-28, Folder 179)
    - Cotten, Thubeua (Box A-28, Folder 180)
      Photographer if identified: Harisch Studios
    - Cotter, Sadie (Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 181)
    - Cotterell, Constance (Box A-28, Folder 182)
    - Cottman, Bonnie (Box A-28, Folder 183)
      Photographer if identified: Irving Fitzig
    - Cotto, David (Rev.) (Box A-28, Folder 184)
    - Cotton Club (Box A-28, Folder 185)
      Also one promotional clipping on lightweight commercial stock.
    - Cotton Comes to Harlem (Box A-28, Folder 186)
    - Cotton, Darlene (Box A-28, Folder 187)
    - Cotton, Elizabeth (Box A-28, Folder 188)
    - Cotton, F. Jane (Miss) (Box A-28, Folder 189)
    - Cotton, Ida (Mrs.) (Box A-28, Folder 190)
    - Cotton, Paul (Box A-28, Folder 191)
    - Cottrell, Clayton (Box A-28, Folder 192)
      Also a typescript newsletter called "black news digest" from the United States Department of Labor/Office of Information Publications and Reports. 12 leaves.
    - Cottrell, Edward (Box A-28, Folder 193)
    - Cottrell, Louis A. (Box A-28, Folder 194)
    - Cottrol, Cheryl (Box A-28, Folder 195)
    - Cottrol, Robert (Bob) (Box A-28, Folder 196)
    - Cottrol, Robert, Jr. (Box A-28, Folder 197)
      Two prints showing Robert Cottroll, Jr., son of freelance photographer Robert W. Cottroll. Three prints showing football players that were taken by Robert W. Cottroll (Sr.)
    - Coty, Robert (Box A-28, Folder 198)
    - Couche, Robert (Box A-28, Folder 199)
      Photographer if identified: Arden Photo Studio, Gill Photographers, Harris Photo
    - Couche, Robert (Box A-28, Folder 200)
    - Coulibaly, Thomas (Box A-28, Folder 201)
    - Coulter, Carl B. (Box A-28, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: Victor B. Greene
    - Coulter, Darrell (Box A-28, Folder 203)
    - Coulter, Hazel (Box A-28, Folder 204)
    - Coulthurst, Audley E. (Box A-28, Folder 205)
    - Coulthurst, Eric (Box A-28, Folder 206)
    - Coulthurst, Lionell L. (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 207)
    - Coulthurst, Milton (Box A-28, Folder 208)
    - Council of Black Elected Democrats (Box A-28, Folder 209)
      Also one ms. letter to editor paperclipped.
    - Council of Concerned Black Americans (Box A-28, Folder 210)
    - Council of Concerned Black Executives (Box A-28, Folder 211)
    - Council of Concerned Black Executives (Box A-28, Folder 212)
    - Council on Economic Development (Box A-28, Folder 213)
    - Council for Economic Opportunities (Box A-28, Folder 214)
    - Council of Police Societies (Box A-28, Folder 215)
    - "Countdown at..." (Box A-28, Folder 216)
    - Convay, Don (Box A-28, Folder 217)
    - Coursey, Henry Ellis (Box A-28, Folder 218)
    - Cousin Joe (Box A-28, Folder 219)
    - Coursey, Leon (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 220)
    - Cousin, Philip (Box A-28, Folder 221)
    - Cousins, L. (Box A-28, Folder 222)
    - Couther, William (Box A-28, Folder 223)
      Photographer if identified: Jaacov Agor
    - Couze, Robert A. (Box A-28, Folder 224)
    - Couture, Dimitri (Box A-28, Folder 225)
    - Couvatier, Natalia (Box A-28, Folder 226)
    - Countee Cullen Community Center (Box A-28, Folder 227)
      Modern color print.
    - Countryman, Bob (Box A-28, Folder 228)
      Photographer if identified: UConn Photo
    - Counts, The (Box A-28, Folder 229)
    - Counts, Johnny (Box A-28, Folder 230)
    - Courcy, Jo Ann (Box A-28, Folder 231)
    - Coursey, Almira K. (Box A-28, Folder 232)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Dave Greene
    - Coursey, Leon N. (Dr.) (Box A-28, Folder 233)
    - Coursey, Richard Louis (Box A-28, Folder 234)
    - Courtney, Ernest (Box A-28, Folder 235)
      Portrait mounted on heavy board.
    - Courtlandt, Henry A. (Box A-28, Folder 236)
    - Courtney, Lon (Box A-28, Folder 237)
    - Courts (Box A-28, Folder 238)
    - Coverdale, Charles A. (Box A-28, Folder 239)
    - Cavett, Dick (Box A-28, Folder 240)
    - Covington, Carol (See Glen Covington) (Box A-28, Folder 241)
    - Covington, Elenore (Box A-28, Folder 242)
    - Covington, Elizabeth (Miss) (Box A-28, Folder 243)
    - Covington, Ella (Box A-28, Folder 244)
    - Covington, George Donald (Box A-28, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Jan Studios, James Gilbert
    - Covington, Glen (Wife and Daughter Carol) (Box A-28, Folder 246)
    - Covington, James (Box A-28, Folder 247)
    - Covington, Lacy (and Rev.) (Box A-28, Folder 248)
    - Covington, Marthetta (Box A-28, Folder 249)
      Also one strip of two black and white negatives